module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'When was the surprise attack by Japan on Pearl Harbor?', 
    a: 'December 7 1941',
    b: 'December 14 1941',
    c: 'December 7 1940',
    d: 'December 14 1942',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the official Hawaiian state team sport?', 
    a: 'Baseball',
    b: 'Soccer',
    c: 'Outrigger canoe paddling',
    d: 'Beach Volleyball',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The nickname for the island of Ni\'ihau is ____', 
    a: 'The Gathering Place',
    b: 'The Garden Isle',
    c: 'The Pineapple Isle',
    d: 'The Forbidden Isle',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the official Hawaiian state mammal?', 
    a: 'Hawaiian monk seal',
    b: 'Northern Elephant Seal',
    c: 'Indian Mongoose',
    d: 'Loggerhead Turtle',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the warmest temperature ever recorded in Hawaii?', 
    a: '97 F',
    b: '99 F',
    c: '102 F',
    d: '100 F',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'The only royal palace in the United States is the ____ palace in Honolulu.', 
    a: 'Kahuna',
    b: 'Mo\'i',
    c: 'Keko',
    d: 'Iolani',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'The ancient Hawaiian code of conduct is called ____', 
    a: 'aloha',
    b: 'kapu',
    c: 'muana',
    d: 'lilo',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'If a person broke kapu, the punishment included ____', 
    a: 'punished by the powerful gods',
    b: 'being hunted by \'ilamuku and drowned',
    c: 'flee to pu\'uhonua (place of forgiveness) for kahuna rituals',
    d: 'all of the above',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'People in Hawaii consume ____ cans of span yearly', 
    a: '6 million',
    b: '600 thousand',
    c: '60 thousand',
    d: '6 thousand',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Hand sign, commonly known as "hang loose"', 
    a: 'katana',
    b: 'shaka',
    c: 'moraka',
    d: 'waimea',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];